<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on Get Forked</title><link>https://getforked.recipes/</link><description>Recent content in Home on Get Forked</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:53:55 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://getforked.recipes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beniamino's Red Sauce</title><link>https://getforked.recipes/recipes/beniaminos-red-sauce/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://getforked.recipes/recipes/beniaminos-red-sauce/</guid><description>This is it, this is my tomato sauce. Do it this way or DIE haha just kidding, it&amp;rsquo;s good though. And use the anchovies, they dissolve, it&amp;rsquo;s fine. Skip &amp;rsquo;em and sub the butter for more olive oil if you need it vegan.
This recipe is modified from Kenji&amp;rsquo;s to be lazier.
&amp;mdash; Ben Ingredients 1 6lb can of San Marzanos (Costco&amp;rsquo;s big ol cans do it just fine) 2 Carrots, washed and with the greens trimmed off 1 yellow onion 3 stalks of celery 2 whole anchovies in olive oil Half a stick of salted butter An entire head of garlic, more or less peeled 1/4 cup olive oil Juice of half a lemon Optional: The anchovies are not optional, nice try.</description></item><item><title>Cajun Benny's Red Beans</title><link>https://getforked.recipes/recipes/cajun-bennys-red-beans/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://getforked.recipes/recipes/cajun-bennys-red-beans/</guid><description>Ingredients 2 cans of red beans (or pinto beans) 4 pieces&amp;rsquo; bacon grease 1/2 cup Water Salt Smoked paprika Cooked white rice (instructions not included) Instructions Cook the bacon in a high-walled pan (such as a cast iron skillet) Pour 2 cans of beans directly into the skillet, bean-water and all. Do not rinse, do not pass go, dump the whole thing in. Bring the bean water to boil, then turn down heat to simmer.</description></item><item><title>THE Shrimp Etouffee</title><link>https://getforked.recipes/recipes/the-shrimp-etouffee/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://getforked.recipes/recipes/the-shrimp-etouffee/</guid><description>I had the best gat dang crawfish etouffee of my life in a pub in New Orleans in like 2016 and I&amp;rsquo;ve been chasing that dragon ever since. This recipe steals significantly from a renowned chef known as Cajun Ron, who might not want his exact recipe published, so I will not denote which pieces come from him or from me except in one specific instance. It&amp;rsquo;s very close to that etouffee in New Orleans.</description></item><item><title>Kasley Family Dumplings</title><link>https://getforked.recipes/recipes/kasley-family-dumplings/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://getforked.recipes/recipes/kasley-family-dumplings/</guid><description>Dough 1 cup of mashed potatoes &amp;ndash; russet, boiled and mashed, no milk or butter. 5 cups white flour Tsp salt 4 eggs 1/4 cup milk, or more Mix with stand mixer or food processor until dough pulls off side of bowl.
Beef Filling 2 lbs 80/20 ground beef 1/2 lb ground pork 1 egg Tsp worcestershire sauce Salt and pepper to scent Cheese Filling Sourcing the cheese can prove difficult.</description></item><item><title>Mary Rooney's Irish Soda Bread</title><link>https://getforked.recipes/recipes/mary-rooneys-irish-soda-bread/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://getforked.recipes/recipes/mary-rooneys-irish-soda-bread/</guid><description>Dough 4 cups regular, white flour 1/4 cup white sugar Tsp salt Tsp baking powder Tsp baking soda 1/4 cup salted butter, room temperature 2 cups raisins, mix of regular and golden 1 1/3 cup buttermilk 1 unbeaten egg Egg whites for brushing Directions Mix the first four ingredients (flour, sugar, salt, baking powder). Cut in the butter &amp;ndash; slice into little pieces, drop it throughout the flour mixture, use a fork to cut/moosh it in.</description></item><item><title>Knize Apple Pie</title><link>https://getforked.recipes/recipes/knize-apple-pie/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://getforked.recipes/recipes/knize-apple-pie/</guid><description>Bake at 450 for 10min Then 375 for 40-50min
Filling 1/3 cup packed brown sugar 3/4 cup sugar 1/2 tsp cinnamon 1/4 tsp salt 1 tsp grated lemon rind or juice 2 Tbsp flour 2 Tbsp butter 6 cups apple slices Combine in bowl; cover apples pot [ sic ] butter.
Crust 2 cups flour 1 tsp salt 2/3 cup crisco 5 - 6 tsp cold water Notes Dad texted me this recipe a few months prior to publish via phone pics of old, yellowed cards from a recipe book.</description></item><item><title>Knize Original Desert Dot Com One Hundred Times Chocholate Sugar Time Incorporated</title><link>https://getforked.recipes/recipes/knize-original-dessert-dot-com/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://getforked.recipes/recipes/knize-original-dessert-dot-com/</guid><description>Brownie Recipe Prep Oven at 325 Pam in 9x13 pan, no parchment Mix Ingredients 1 cup flour 1 1/2 cups granulated sugar 2/3 cups confectioner&amp;rsquo;s sugar 4 eggs (room temp, or close to it) 1 cup neutral vegetable oil (canola, probably) 1/2 tsp baking powder 1 tsp salt 2/3 cup cocoa powder 2 to4 tsp vanilla based on how much chocolate you dump in there 1 cup semi-sweet chocolate chips 3/4 cup to 1 1/2 cup of roughly chopped baking chocolate bar.</description></item><item><title>Volrath Thanksgiving Turkey</title><link>https://getforked.recipes/recipes/volrath-thanksgiving-turkey/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://getforked.recipes/recipes/volrath-thanksgiving-turkey/</guid><description>Turkey Dinner Tips We keep these lists from year to year and can add notes about what worked or didn’t work. To sum this whole page up: make a list and stick to it to stay organized! So, read it through once and you will be good to go!
Necessities: a good roasting pan, the foil ones can buckle (Nancy lost a turkey to the floor one year and I had grease ooze out of one that smoked my kitchen) if you have to use a foil pan make sure you have it on a very sturdy cookie sheet with an edge.</description></item><item><title>Westhaven Cake</title><link>https://getforked.recipes/recipes/westhaven-cake/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://getforked.recipes/recipes/westhaven-cake/</guid><description>Ingredients 3/4 cup chopped dates
1 cup hot water
1 tsp baking soda
1/2 cup butter
1 cup sugar
2 egg yolks, beaten
1 3/4 cups flour
1 Tbsp cocoa
2 egg whites, stiffly beaten
1 cup chopped nuts
1 cup chocolate chips
Directions Pour the hot water over the dates, and stir in the baking soda, set aside t ocool. Cream butter, sugar, egg yolks and vanilla. Add date mixture to the butter mixture and beat well.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://getforked.recipes/about/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://getforked.recipes/about/</guid><description>We are not currently accepting submissions.</description></item></channel></rss>