<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Featured on Get Forked</title><link>https://getforked.recipes/tags/featured/</link><description>Recent content in Featured on Get Forked</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:53:55 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://getforked.recipes/tags/featured/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beniamino's Red Sauce</title><link>https://getforked.recipes/recipes/beniaminos-red-sauce/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://getforked.recipes/recipes/beniaminos-red-sauce/</guid><description>This is it, this is my tomato sauce. Do it this way or DIE haha just kidding, it&amp;rsquo;s good though. And use the anchovies, they dissolve, it&amp;rsquo;s fine. Skip &amp;rsquo;em and sub the butter for more olive oil if you need it vegan.
This recipe is modified from Kenji&amp;rsquo;s to be lazier.
&amp;mdash; Ben Ingredients 1 6lb can of San Marzanos (Costco&amp;rsquo;s big ol cans do it just fine) 2 Carrots, washed and with the greens trimmed off 1 yellow onion 3 stalks of celery 2 whole anchovies in olive oil Half a stick of salted butter An entire head of garlic, more or less peeled 1/4 cup olive oil Juice of half a lemon Optional: The anchovies are not optional, nice try.</description></item><item><title>THE Shrimp Etouffee</title><link>https://getforked.recipes/recipes/the-shrimp-etouffee/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://getforked.recipes/recipes/the-shrimp-etouffee/</guid><description>I had the best gat dang crawfish etouffee of my life in a pub in New Orleans in like 2016 and I&amp;rsquo;ve been chasing that dragon ever since. This recipe steals significantly from a renowned chef known as Cajun Ron, who might not want his exact recipe published, so I will not denote which pieces come from him or from me except in one specific instance. It&amp;rsquo;s very close to that etouffee in New Orleans.</description></item><item><title>Kasley Family Dumplings</title><link>https://getforked.recipes/recipes/kasley-family-dumplings/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://getforked.recipes/recipes/kasley-family-dumplings/</guid><description>Dough 1 cup of mashed potatoes &amp;ndash; russet, boiled and mashed, no milk or butter. 5 cups white flour Tsp salt 4 eggs 1/4 cup milk, or more Mix with stand mixer or food processor until dough pulls off side of bowl.
Beef Filling 2 lbs 80/20 ground beef 1/2 lb ground pork 1 egg Tsp worcestershire sauce Salt and pepper to scent Cheese Filling Sourcing the cheese can prove difficult.</description></item></channel></rss>